<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TekkenWiki</string>

    <string name="AkumaWiki">
        Акума появляется как гостевой персонаж в Tekken 7: Fated Retribution. \n
        В истории игры он стремится вернуть долг Кадзуми Мисима, которая просит его убить её мужа Хэйхати и сына Кадзую после своей смерти.\n
        Как и в Street Fighter, Акума заменяет Кадзуми в качестве секретного аркадного финального босса при определённых условиях
        У Акумы тёмно-рыжие волосы, тёмная кожа, светящиеся красные глаза с чёрной склерой, носит на шее чётки, одет в тёмно-серый каратэги и пояс вокруг его талии вместо оби.\n
        Кандзи «тэн» (天) — означает «Небеса» — можно увидеть на его спине, когда оно появляется во время определённых анимаций победы.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="AlisaWiki">
       Алиса Босконович (アリサ・ボスコノビッチ Arisa Bosukonobicchi на Японском) персонаж серии Tekken, которая появилась в​ Tekken 6: Bloodline Rebellion. Она - андроид, созданный Доктором Босконовичем.
    \n
        Об Алисе известно очень мало, кроме её имени и создателя.  Алиса была создана вышеупомянутым Доктором Босконовичем. Согласно её прологу в Tekken 6, больше ничего не известно о её прошлой жизни. Кроме создателя Алисы, лишь немногие знают, что она является роботом, а именно: Линь Сяою, Дзин Кадзама, Нина Уильямс, Анна Уильямс, Казуя Мишима и её партнер Ларс Александерссон.
    </string>

    <string name="AnnaWiki">
       (アンナ・ウィリアムズ Anna Williams) - один из самых популярных женских персонажей серии наряду с её сестрой. Родилась и выросла в Ирландии. Младшая сестра Нины Уильямс. Она изучала боевые искусства Хапкидо и Айкидо у своей матери, чемпиона в женском первенстве по Айкидо. В то время как отец сестёр, Ричард Уильямс, обучал старшую сестру технике Ассасина, он не уделял внимание Анне, так и не обучив ее этой технике. Анна появляется во всех частях серии, кроме четвёртой.
После смерти отца - Ричарда Уильямса между сестрами Анной и Ниной возникает ненависть на всю оставшуюся жизнь, обвиняя друг друга в его смерти их вражда усиливается с каждым днём.
    </string>
    <string name="ArmorWiki">
       Armor King (アーマー・キング Āmā Kingu?) is a title that two characters have taken in the Tekken series. Even though there have been two characters who have taken the name, each is simply called Armor King in their respective games, though a numerical value is sometimes given to them to separate them as different characters, similar to King.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="AsukaWiki">
      Asuka Kazama (風間 飛鳥 Kazama Asuka?) is a character in the Tekken series who was first introduced in Tekken 5 and she has returned for every subsequent game in the series. While she was originally purported to be the cousin of Jin Kazama and the niece of Jun Kazama, it has later been stated by Katsuhiro Harada (see below) that their relationship is more complicated than that.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="BryanWiki">
       Bryan Fury (ブライアン・フューリー Buraian Fyūrī?) is a character in the Tekken fighting game series. Bryan first appeared in Tekken 3, and he has returned in all subsequent Tekken games. Bryan is popular among fans for his ruthless personality, hard-hitting fighting style and trademark evil laugh.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="HeihachiWiki">
       Heihachi Mishima (三島 平八 Mishima Heihachi?) is one of the main characters in the Tekken series. He debuted in the first game in the series and has returned for all subsequent titles. Though seen as the main protagonist and anti-villain of the second game, he is the main antagonist of the series as he is almost always responsible for the events. His impact on the story has seemed to decrease since Tekken 5 as he has become a minor character to the storyline, but in Tekken 7, Heihachi again became part of the main storyline and returned as the principal antagonist, and villain protagonist of the game. Heihachi is the son of Jinpachi Mishima, the husband of Kazumi Mishima, the father of Kazuya Mishima and Lars Alexandersson, the adoptive father of Lee Chaolan, and the grandfather of Jin Kazama.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="JinWiki">
       Jin Kazama (風間 仁 Kazama Jin?) is one of the main characters of the Tekken series. He is featured on the packaging for the console version of almost every sequel following his introduction in Tekken 3. He has been the main protagonist for the majority of the following entries ever since his debut in Tekken 3, and has been trying to end the Mishima Bloodline to save the world from their evil.

The exception to this was when he took on an anti-villain role in Tekken 6 (with Lars Alexandersson taking his role as the protagonist), and also when he took on the role of a supporting character in Tekken 7 (where Heihachi Mishima and Kazuya Mishima became the main characters of the game). Jin is the son of Kazuya Mishima and Jun Kazama, the grandson of Heihachi Mishima and Kazumi Mishima, the adoptive nephew of Lee Chaolan, the half-nephew of Lars Alexandersson, a relative to Asuka Kazama, and the great-grandson of Jinpachi Mishima.\n
        \n
    </string>



    <string name="KunimitsuWiki">
       Kunimitsu (州光?) is a title given to two kunoichi characters in the Tekken fighting game series.

The first Kunimitsu made her first appearance in the original Tekken as an unlockable character who acted as the sub-boss for Michelle Chang. She later retires at the end of her last canonical appearance, Tekken 2, and is succeeded by her daughter in Tekken 7.

Both Kunimitsu I and Kunimitsu II are kunoichis who wear Fox masks, and utilize respective close-ranged weapons.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="LarsWiki">
        Акума появляется как гостевой персонаж в Tekken 7: Fated Retribution. \n
        В истории игры он стремится вернуть долг Кадзуми Мисима, которая просит его убить её мужа Хэйхати и сына Кадзую после своей смерти.\n
        Как и в Street Fighter, Акума заменяет Кадзуми в качестве секретного аркадного финального босса при определённых условиях
        У Акумы тёмно-рыжие волосы, тёмная кожа, светящиеся красные глаза с чёрной склерой, носит на шее чётки, одет в тёмно-серый каратэги и пояс вокруг его талии вместо оби.\n
        Кандзи «тэн» (天) — означает «Небеса» — можно увидеть на его спине, когда оно появляется во время определённых анимаций победы.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="LawWiki">
      Lars Alexandersson (ラース・アレクサンダーソン Rāsu Arekusandāson?) is one of the main characters of the Tekken series since his first introduction in Tekken 6: Bloodline Rebellion and is the main protagonist of that game and later one of the main protagonists in Tekken 7. \n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="LuckyWiki">
        Lucky Chloe (ラッキークロエ Rakkī Kuroe?) is a character in the Tekken series who was introduced in Tekken 7 as one of the new playable characters\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="YoshimitsuWiki">
Yoshimitsu (吉光?) is a fictional character who was first introduced in the original Tekken game and has returned for all subsequent sequels in the Tekken series (primarily in main series installments due to his absence in some spin-off installments, Tekken Revolution). Additionally, an analogous character bearing the same name, weapon, clan, and basic information was later carried over into Namcos Soul series of fighting games as a major character, making his debut in the second game of the series, Soulcalibur, and has returned for all of the series main installments.\n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="ZafinaWiki">
        Zafina (Arabic: زافينا Zāfīnā, Japanese: ザフィーナ Zafīna) is a playable character in the Tekken series. She was introduced in Tekken 6 and appeared in Tekken Tag Tournament 2. She returns in Tekken 7 as a DLC character included in the third season pass.\n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_akuma">AkumaActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_anna">AnnaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_alisa">AlisaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_armor">ArmorActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_asuka">AsukaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bryan">BryanActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jin">JinActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_zafina">ZafinaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_yoshimitsu">YoshimitsuActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kadzumi">KadzumiActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kunimitsu">KunimitsuActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lucky">LuckyActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lars">LarsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_law">LawActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_heihachi">HeihachiActivity</string>
</resources>